{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Bug \u0026 Insect Exterminators","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40353/":{"taskOID":40353,"originalTaskOID":40353,"setID":647,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1224,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Insects","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of insects do you need to be controlled? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":795,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ants","answerDisplayText":"Ants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","answerDisplayText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Beetles","answerDisplayText":"Beetles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cockroaches","answerDisplayText":"Cockroaches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fleas","answerDisplayText":"Fleas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2523,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flies","answerDisplayText":"Flies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3439,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ladybugs","answerDisplayText":"Ladybugs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203144,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mites","answerDisplayText":"Mites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203932,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Mosquitos","answerDisplayText":"Mosquitos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5948,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Spiders","answerDisplayText":"Spiders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6298,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Termites","answerDisplayText":"Termites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5536,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Control Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of control service do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4656,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pest evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Pest evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Recurring pest control service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring pest control service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fumigation","answerDisplayText":"Fumigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4399,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6294,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Termite inspection and report","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection and report","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500603,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of home:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"Square footage of home:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 3000","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1224,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Insects","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of insects do you need to be controlled? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":795,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ants","answerDisplayText":"Ants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","answerDisplayText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Beetles","answerDisplayText":"Beetles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cockroaches","answerDisplayText":"Cockroaches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fleas","answerDisplayText":"Fleas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2523,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flies","answerDisplayText":"Flies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3439,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ladybugs","answerDisplayText":"Ladybugs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203144,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mites","answerDisplayText":"Mites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203932,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Mosquitos","answerDisplayText":"Mosquitos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5948,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Spiders","answerDisplayText":"Spiders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6298,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Termites","answerDisplayText":"Termites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":795,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ants","answerDisplayText":"Ants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","answerDisplayText":"Bees, Hornets or Wasps ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1012,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Beetles","answerDisplayText":"Beetles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cockroaches","answerDisplayText":"Cockroaches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fleas","answerDisplayText":"Fleas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2523,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flies","answerDisplayText":"Flies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3439,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ladybugs","answerDisplayText":"Ladybugs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203144,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mites","answerDisplayText":"Mites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203932,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Mosquitos","answerDisplayText":"Mosquitos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5948,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Spiders","answerDisplayText":"Spiders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6298,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Termites","answerDisplayText":"Termites","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5536,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Control Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of control service do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4656,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pest evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Pest evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Recurring pest control service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring pest control service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fumigation","answerDisplayText":"Fumigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4399,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6294,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Termite inspection and report","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection and report","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4656,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pest evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Pest evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Recurring pest control service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring pest control service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fumigation","answerDisplayText":"Fumigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4399,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite treatment service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6294,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Termite inspection and report","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection and report","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500603,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of home:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"Square footage of home:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 3000","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17662,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200828,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 3000","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376527473pwspr007F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40353/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40353,"taskName":"Pest Control - Bugs and Insects","taskDescription":"Pest Control - Bugs \u0026 Insects","xmTaskDescriptor":"Bug \u0026 Insect Exterminators","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":137,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Control Insects Pest Bugs ant","textMessagingName":"Pest Control Bug","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes the reduction or extermination of flying, crawling \u0026 boring bugs.","rolloverShortDesc":"Pest control or exterminator.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Pest Control - Bugs \u0026 Insects.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Exterminators \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Bed Bug \u0026 Insect Control","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":58,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bug \u0026 Insect Control","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pest Control - Bugs and Insects","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pest Control Project","urlName":"Pest-Control-Bugs-and-Insects","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Exterminators - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Bed Bug, Insect Control","searchKeywords":"Insects,Pest,Bugs,ant,exterminator,pesticide,termite,pesticides,exterminators,electronic, bedbugs, hives, bees, roaches, roach","emcCategoryOid":-12057,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":647,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}